an online City based video game an
expense on your smartphones and such
like you yeah an idea for a game but
where you're mimicking an actual
disaster and seeing how your city would
actually do so like I guess Larkin meets
online gameplay in real life I think
that would be fun
I like Prytania their zombie apocalypse
it scares gonna play more when it's
things that are actually usable and very
likely to happen in my lifetime but
finding the yeah having a simulation to
see okay well could Vancouver survive
there was an earthquake and XY and Z
happen and be into it with everyone else
so especially if you it was a citywide
thing where everyone within downtown
district had to figure out I don't know
how to get food how to wait up food the
whole point is to come up with it to
gather all these ideas when someone
comes up with it just say if it works it
doesn't work what would make it awesome
awesome or I know that's the word so
this was going to be kind of yeah no
this is idea number 82 Apple 82